Good morning, guys.
It's Syd.
I am so happy to be back home.
Every time I come back here, I feel like I just feel so myself.
Like the truest, purest form of me is here.
Why am I getting so introspective?
Like, hello?
I love a lot of things about you guys, but one of my absolute favorite
things is how much you guys not only appreciate but love the Minnesota vlogs.
The feeling of coziness and warmth that I get when I'm home, I always try
to somehow translate onto video.
I don't know if that is even possible, but I hope that you feel comfy
and cozy and at home watching this.
Don't really know what today holds.
I did just get here.
I was in Paris.
I feel like I kind of need a little reset.
And I love a good reset vlog.
Like, I'm such a sucker for a good reset vlog.
I'm gonna go try a new coffee shop this morning before I get changed I
just got this new fragrance in the mail from Fern and I'm so excited to
be working with them some of you guys know I've been like really sensitive to
a lot of products the past couple years so what really drew me to them
is that their fragrances are natural the ingredients are organic and they come out with
four different releases each year per the season so this is their summer fragrance which
I'm so excited to try they do include a little tester bottle so you can
try this out.
Okay this is their summer 2026 bottle.
It's like a fresh summer day.
I wish that there was a way for you to smell this through the screen.
It's perfect.
Their summer one is very citrus focused.
I can really smell the basil which I love fresh basil.
They're also on a made-to-order basis which is pretty cool so they do have limited
quantities per drop.
They did put aside a little batch for you guys so if you do want
to try out their summer fragrance, I put a link in the description box so
you can skip the waiting list and try out their fragrance.
It is so hot today.
I don't know what I'm going to wear.
Ooh, I did just thrift this t-shirt.
Finishing touches.
I'm at a coffee shop.
I'm trying a new one today.
This one, it looks like you can kind of work from home and I have
my laptop to do some stuff on.
It's called Fragment Coffee.
I saw it on TikTok.
You know, this is the place where I do all of my research nowadays it
seems.
Thank you.
This is the biggest coffee shop i have ever been in in my life why
is it massive i always forget coming back home like in new york vlogging and
filming in public it can slide there's a lot of crazy stuff that goes down
in new york but here it's like there's a chess tournament happening to the right
of me and I'm drawing attention to myself.
Apparently this place has been here for like five years and I never knew about
it and I think this is gonna be one of my new spots to come
because it's like so conducive for working from home.
There's pretty much unlimited seating.
Coffee.
I already drank my coffee.
I'm sorry.
The coffee itself is pretty good.
It has like a nutty taste to it.
I also got banana bread because I was hungry.
This is like below average.
Would not recommend.
I'm gonna do some work for Ophelia.
When I was in Paris and stuff, I did nothing for Ophelia.
Then I have so much to do because we're hiring a new social media assistant
and you just schedule like interviews for that.
I had a life-changing event happen to me about two weeks ago in New York.
I was walking actually to meet up with my boyfriend.
It's like the same route that I always take.
I walked past so many paparazzi and there was this black SUV.
Someone was clearly like just about to get out of there and I had no
idea who was in there and two seconds later out walks Rihanna and ASAP Rocky.
I was actually never a massive Rihanna fan like I liked her but ever since
then I've just been captivated by her.
I always get so nostalgic at this corner because this is where the school bus
would pick me up in elementary school.
Growing up in the same house for your entire childhood I think is like one
of the most special things that could have happened to me.
Zero to 18 I grew up in the same house and My parents still have
the exact same house.
Obviously all of my childhood memories just resonate with that house.
It's like a feeling I get every time I come home, even to this day
at age 26, I still get the same feeling when I walk inside.
My brother and I had a lemonade stand right here.
At this point, I'm not even walking Rosie.
Rosie is walking me because
rosie is so tired hi that's such a good workout we're so fit i know
i'm so tired too my parents set up badminton in the backyard so we're gonna
play whose team am I on?
Mine.
Champions.
Oh god.
I kind of suck at this.
My hand-eye coordination I feel has deteriorated the past few years.
Is that old age or what?
I don't know.
Okay.
Who do you think's gonna win?
We got it.
I'm not on your team.
I know.
that's what I said we got oh so not me the rules are no blood
no foul so the best team wins okay what does that mean
good morning guys it's Sunday I woke up this morning and I went to church
with my family and now it's noon.
My family is kind of dispersed for a little bit.
We're gonna go to my older brother's house later.
I have an older brother.
Do you guys know this?
I feel like so many people don't know that I have an older brother and
one of my favorite things to do when I'm home is drive around, get coffee
at a drive-thru, and listen to music and then maybe go to the Mall of
America.
Sort of where my head's at.
We'll see kind of what ends up happening.
I don't really know.
To those of you who don't know what caribou is, I'm about to introduce you.
The real ones know who have watched me for years that I used to hate
coffee.
I hated coffee to such an extent that I feel like it was almost part
of my personality.
Anyways, I've turned a new leaf.
You know I love coffee now, so I really appreciate what Caribou has to offer
now that I can enjoy it.
Could I do an iced medium latte with skim milk?
I just think the coffee here is pretty good.
My grandpa always used to love it, and I was like, why?
I don't want to go to Caribou.
And now I feel bad because like He was right all along.
Oh, my credit card is just flashing out so everyone can use it.
Usually what I get from here is an iced vanilla craft of press, skim milk
and a scoop of malt.
Malt makes it so good.
Thank you.
I'm putting my usual order on the screen for you guys because you, if you
live in Minnesota or the Midwest, I think they have these in the Midwest, you
need to try my go-to.
Anyways, today I was boring.
I just got a vanilla latte because I was in the mood.
It's always this or Dunkin' for me when I'm home.
So cheers.
Summer in Minnesota is the best.
Every time I go home, I have to go to the Mall of America at
least once.
By the way, the best thing that the Mall of America ever opened was Skims.
When I found out they were putting this in there, I was so happy.
I stopped there, Aritzia, a few stores.
Okay, update.
I've been pretty good.
I only got one thing from Skims.
It's their t-shirt.
I literally wore mine all the time until I lost it.
So I feel like I could justify that.
I don't know if I was late to this, but the Lululemon here has a
cafe where they have like the best smoothies.
So it's like a good little healthy shopping snack.
At this point, like forget an Erewhon.
I don't even care.
I just want to get the Lululemon smoothie.
Okay, okay.
Okay, what do I have?
Hey guys!
Hey there.
I'm with my older brother, Ryan.
That's me.
I don't think that they know, I don't think that they know about you.
I'm Ryan.
I'm Sydney's brother.
I live in Minnesota.
And he's a chef.
Look what he just made us.
Wow.
So homemade.
Uh-huh.
Thank you.
So you made the dough yourself?
Oh, yeah.
All by myself.
Update.
I changed into a pickleball outfit.
As some of you guys know, I used to be an avid pickleball hater.
And now, somehow I love it.
It's kind of like the coffee thing.
I used to, like, hate both of these things.
Is this like me maturing?
I don't know.
My family and I love to play together.
It's like such a fun family activity for us.
And you already know what I'm about to say.
I forgot an outro.
Please let me know if you do have any videos you want to see.
I know I say this sometimes, but I really do read the comments.
And I'll see you guys in my next vlog.
Bye!
you